A Guide to the Tom Buckley Collection on Virginia Political Campaign Memorabilia, 1963-2009 (bulk 1969-1983)
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 4: Posters, 1966-1994
  - T. Farrell Egge (Board of Supervisors), Undated
  - Gary P. Eklund (Delegate), 1977
  - Joseph L. Fisher (U.S. Senate) (2 copies), Undated
  - Joseph V. Gartlan, Jr. (State Senate) (3 copies), Undated
  - Virgil H. Goode, Jr. (U.S. Senate), Undated
  - Herbert E. Harris, II (House of Representatives), 1974
  - Herbert E. Harris, II (House of Representatives) (2 copies), Undated
  - Herbert E. Harris, II (House of Representatives) (2 copies), Undated
  - Herbert E. Harris, II (House of Representatives), Undated
  - Herbert E. Harris, II (House of Representatives), Undated
  - Herbert E. Harris, II (House of Representatives) (3 copies), Undated
  - Herbert E. Harris, II (House of Representatives), Undated
  - Robert E. Harris (Delegate), Undated
  - Edythe C. Harrison (U.S. Senate), 1984
  - John F. "Jack" Herrity, Undated
  - John F. "Jack" Herrity (Chair, Board of Supervisors), Undated
  - John F. "Jack" Herrity (Chair, Board of Supervisors), Undated
  - John F. "Jack" Herrity (House of Representatives), 1978
  - Omer L. Hirst (State Senate), Undated
  - Jon D. Holstine (Board of Supervisors), 1979
  - Robert F. Horan, Jr., Undated
  - Robert F. Horan, Jr. (House of Representatives), 1972
  - Henry E. Howell, Jr. (Governor), 1977
  - Henry E. Howell, Jr. (Governor), 1977
  - Henry E. Howell, Jr. (Governor), 1977
  - Henry E. Howell, Jr. (Governor), Undated
  - Henry E. Howell, Jr./Charles S. Robb/Edward E. Lane (2 copies), Undated
  - M. Wayne Huggins (Sheriff), 1979
  - Gerald W. Hyland (Board of Supervisors), Undated
  - Gerald W. Hyland (Board of Supervisors), Undated
  - Gerald W. Hyland (House of Representatives) (2 copies), 1975
  - Gerald W. Hyland (House of Representatives), 1975
  - Charles E. Kaufman (Delegate), 1979
  - Gladys B. Keating (Delegate) (2 copies), Undated
  - Gladys B. Keating (Delegate) (2 copies), Undated
  - Gladys B. Keating (Delegate), Undated
  - Gladys B. Keating (Delegate), Undated
  - Gladys B. Keating (Delegate), Undated
  - Jane M. King (Delegate), 1979
  - Elaine A. Lailas (Delegate), 1981
  - Henry C. Mackall (Delegate), 1969
  - Frank E. Mann (House of Representatives), 1974
  - Randolph J. May (Delegate), 1975
  - Virginia McEnearney (Delegate), 1973
  - Virginia McEnearney (Board of Supervisors), Undated
  - John L. Melnick (Attorney General), 1977
  - John L. Melnick (Attorney General) (2 copies), 1977
  - Andrew P. Miller - Attorney General, Undated
  - Andrew P. Miller (Governor), 1977
  - Andrew P. Miller (U.S. Senate), 1978
  - Harold O. Miller (House of Representatives), 1972
  - Myron Mintz (Board of Supervisors), 1971
  - Walter Mondale/Geraldine Ferraro -(Presidential), 1984
  - Oliver North (U.S. Senate), 1974
  - Jerry Norton (Delegate), Undated
  - Jean Packard (Chair, Board of Supervisors), 1975
  - Jean Packard (State Senate), 1979
  - Stanford E. Parris (House of Representatives) (anti-Parris paid for by Herb Harris) (3 copies), 1988
  - Stanford E. Parris (House of Representatives) (2 copies), Undated
  - Stanford E. Parris (Delegate), Undated
  - Kenneth R. Plum (Delegate), Undated
  - Lawrence D. Pratt (Delegate), Undated
  - Joseph D. Ragan (Board of Supervisors), Undated
  - Richard S. "Major" Reynolds (Lieutenant Governor) (3 copies), 1977
  - Richard S. "Major" Reynolds (Lieutenant Governor) (2 copies), 1977
  - Richard S. "Major" Reynolds (Lieutenant Governor), 1977
  - Richard S. "Major" Reynolds (Lieutenant Governor), 1977
  - Marie W. Ridder (Delegate), 1982
  - Charles S. Robb (Lieutenant Governor), 1977
  - Charles S. Robb (Governor) (3 copies), 1981
  - Charles S. Robb (U.S. Senate), 1994
  - Charles S. Robb (U.S. Senate), 1994
  - Charles S. Robb/Leslie S. Byrne (anti-Democrat), 1994
  - Charles S. Robb/Richard J. Davis/Gerald L. Baliles, Undated
  - Charles S. Robb/Richard J. Davis/Gerald L. Baliles, Undated
  - Charles S. Robb/Richard J. Davis/Gerald L. Baliles, Undated
  - Richard Saslaw (House of Representatives), Undated
  - Richard Saslaw (House of Representatives), Undated
  - Richard Saslaw (Delegate), 1977
  - Richard Saslaw (State Senate), Undated
  - Richard Saslaw (State Senate) (3 copies), Undated
  - Jim Scott (Board of Supervisors) (2 copies), Undated
  - William Scott (House of Representatives), Undated
  - Shad Solomon (Attorney General) (2 copies), 1977
  - Shad Solomon (Attorney General) (3 copies), 1977
  - Shad Solomon (Attorney General), 1977
  - Nora Anderson Squyres (Delegate), 1982
  - Vernon LeRoy "Lee" Strang, Jr. (Delegate), Undated
  - George W. Stroube (Delegate), 1975
  - James D. Swinson (Sheriff), Undated
  - Jim Tate (House of Representatives), Undated
  - David L. Temple (Delegate), 1982
  - Robert L. Thoburn (Delegate), Undated
  - Charles L. Waddell (State Senate), Undated
  - John B. Watkins, IV (State Senate), Undated
  - Vivian Watts (Chair, Board of Supervisors), 1979
  - Carrington Williams, Undated
  - Carrington Williams/Harold A. Valentine/Dorothy S. McDiarmid/Raymond E. Vickery Jr./Kenneth R. Plum (Delegate)s, 1975
  - Ken Wilson (Sheriff), 1979
  - Frank Wolf (House of Representatives), Undated
  - Vote to End Blue Laws, Undated